You've looked at where your users come from and how they behave on your site.
你已经查看了你的用户来自哪里以及他们在你网站上的行为
But you may also have an action from the user in
但是 你也可以从用户的角度采取
mind that aligns with your business objectives.
与你的业务目标一致的行动
In order to measure how well your site or app fulfills your objectives,
为了衡量你的网站或应用程序是否有实现你的目标
you can tell Google Analytics what ideal behavior looks
你可以通过设定目标告诉 Google Analytics
like on your site through the process of setting up goals.
你网站上的理想行为是什么样
Goals are a way to track valuable actions you would like to see on your website.
通过目标 你可以跟踪你想在你的网站上看到的有价值的行动
The goal is where you define the action you would like to see.
目标是定义你想要看到的行动
Completion of that valuable action itself is referred to as a conversion.
完成该有价值行动本身被称为转化
Conversions could be things like a purchase,
转化可以是购买、
a download and an email subscription et cetera.
下载和电子邮件订阅等等
So goals and conversions always go hand in hand.
所以目标和转化总是齐头并进的
You count conversions and the goals are
你可以计算转化次数 而目标是
a way to define what you will consider a conversion.
定义你认为的转化
Let's take a quick look at different types of companies and
让我们快速查看不同类型的公司
their objectives and the related Google Analytics goals.
及其目标以及相关的 Google Analytics 目标
We talked about Betabrand before.
我们之前谈到过 Betabrand
One of the main objectives of their website is to sell products.
他们网站的主要目标之一是销售产品
So desired action on the website would be behavior that leads to a transaction.
所以在网站上想要的行动是导致交易的行为
In Betabrand's case, a goal in
在 Betabrand 的案例中 Google Analytics 的目标
Google Analytics would just be a transaction or a product sale.
是一个交易或产品销售
BambooHR. is a B2B site.
BambooHR  是一个 B2B 网站
They don't expect people to buy their product on the website,
他们不是希望人们在网站上购买他们的产品
but they want visitors to ask for more information.
而是希望访客询问更多的信息
So one of their goals could be to get people to fill out a request form for a live demo.
所以他们的目标之一就是让人们填写一个现场演示的请求表单
As you can see the nature of the goals differs
正如你所看到的
depending on the nature of the site and the objectives.
目标的性质取决于网站的性质和目标
Typically goals fall into five types and in the next section,
通常目标分为五种类型 在下一节中
we will define what those five types are.
我们将定义这五种类型
But there's one more concept you need to understand when setting up goals.
但是在设定目标时你还需要了解更多的概念
While you may have one big important goal in mind,
虽然你心里可能有一个大的重要目标
there are often several smaller steps a user
但是在完成你的大目标之前
goes through before completing your big goal.
用户需要经过几个较小的步骤
We refer to them as micro goals.
我们把它们称为微观目标
These micro goals are important smaller steps that lead to the bigger macro goal.
这些微观目标是实现更大宏观目标的重要小步骤
When a micro goal is achieved we talk about
当微观目标实现时 我们称其为微观转化
micro conversion and a macro goal relates to macro conversions.
而宏观目标与宏观转化有关
In the case of Betabrand for instance,
以 Betabrand 为例
the macro goal is to have users purchase a product,
宏观目标是让用户购买一个产品
so a macro conversion would be a completed purchase.
所以宏观转化是一个完成的购买行为
But there may be other micro goals that help to achieve this.
但是 可能有其他的微观目标有助于实现这一目标
For instance Betabrand uses newsletters to let
例如 Betabrand 使用新闻简讯
potential customers know about new products or promotions.
让潜在客户了解新产品或促销信息
These e-mails help to get users to come to the site and buy a product.
这些电子邮件有助于让用户来到网站并购买产品
But in order for Betabrand to send these newsletters,
但为了让 Betabrand 发送这些简讯
they need users to sign up for them thus
他们需要用户注册
signing up for the newsletter could be considered a micro goal,
因此注册简讯可以被认为是一个微观目标
because Betabrand assumes it will ultimately lead to the macro goal to purchase.
因为 Betabrand 认为它最终会导向购买这个宏观目标